Hello friends, welcome to Stock Market Manta.
Hope
all of you are happy and happy.  Friends, all the
videos made on this channel are
only for educational purposes.
Friends, we are talking about the results of Q4
and yesterday the results of many companies
came.  Let me present before
you the results of some selected companies.  A
disclaimer friends, there
is no recommendation on any share and if you
want results on any company or
when is the result of that company, you will comment then
I will make a video on it and upload it
friends, let us see
about the company friends, the name of the company is Elcon
Engineering Company, there
is a benefit for its share holder friends that this company has
given a dividend of ₹1.5, now let us see
how much the company has earned friends.  So
before that let's see the sequence.  31st
March 2026, 31st December 2025 and 31st
March 2005.  That's it friends for our year
end year comparison and that's it for
our quarter end quarter comparison.  Let's see
how much the company has earned.  So
in the last quarter the company had earned Rs
5759.
Now how much have you done in this quarter?  2638 You
can see friends, there
is a jump in profit quarter after quarter.  Now let's see
friends how is Yearly?  So
look at yearly 816
and how much is there in this quarter?  7638
So you can see that year and year the profit of the company is
down.  Now let us see
how much the company has spent to earn so much,
friends.  So the company has spent a
total of 62102 friends,
when we will do income minus expense friends, we get
two things, either profit
or loss, so the company is in profit
friends and profit before all like
tax interest exceptional item, before that
we call the company profit before
interest and tax PBBT, so that is
friends 14200 26, now how much was it in the last quarter
and how much was it last year 18956,
so here also friends you can see that
quarter to quarter profit of the company is
jump but year to year it
is down, now friends let us come
after subtracting tax taxes, but let me tell you one more thing
friends, the company has
shown a loss of 10177 37 in exceptional item.  For this reason, the
profit of this quarter has come down very rapidly.  You
can see what is called profit for the period.
Friends, this is the profit which will be published everywhere on news channels, websites,
which is only Rs 600.
Why this?  Because the company has suffered a loss in exceptional items
which is Rs 10177,
how much was it in the last quarter?  7199
and how much was it last year?  14648
So friends, the profit of this quarter
is very low and year end, revenue
and profit were everything.  But the
reason for this quarter being down is these
exceptional items.  Now let's come to EPS
friends. EPS also 0.27, 3.21 &
6.53.  So you can see that EPS is also down in the same way,
friends.  So now let's come to the
next company friends the name of the company
is GTPL LED friends this also has
good news for its shareholders friends
because this company has also given a dividend of ₹ 2
friends now let's see
how much the company has earned so see
friends before that what is the sequence
31st March 2026 31st December 2025 and 31st
March 2025 the sequence is correct friends now let's come to the
total income.
Friends, the total income of the company is Rs 9344.2
and how much did it earn in the previous quarter
?  9381 can you
see friends
can you say flattish performance and how much did you do last year
?  8989 You
can say quarter and quarter
is a very flat performance.  But friends, there is a jump in the year-
end profit, which is the total income and is
called revenue.  Now
how much has the company spent to earn so much
?  So friends, see the company has spent Rs
9545.2,
so one thing has to be remembered friends.  The company
incurred high expenses.  So when we subtract income and expenses,
we will either incur
profit or loss.  So the company has incurred losses,
friends.  See, at 200.91 the
company went from direct profit to loss.
Why?  Because look at the last quarter at
149.81 and the year before that at 124, the
company has gone straight into loss from 149.  Now let us see
what tax will be levied on this, but still let us see
friends, after
adding and subtracting all the tax, exceptional items,
for the period loss, we will say
friends, not profit, the quarterly
loss is 139.2,
how much was the profit in the first quarter,
how much was it last year, 108, so friends, the PAT of this quarter has
come
in negative, which will be called cross 139.2, the
same thing will be visible to us in EPS also
friends.  See, negative EPS has come 1.34
and 0.98 and 0.95, so from 0.95 it is directly negative
- 1.34.  0.98 again minus 38 now let's come to the
last company.  Friends, the
name of the last company is ICICI
General Insurance Company.  One more thing friends, it is
not that easy to read the results of the insurance company.  I should tell you in advance
but I will still try to tell you after reading it carefully.
Friends, there is good news for the shareholders of this company also.
Friends, the company has given a dividend of ₹7.
That too is the final dividend.  What does one
say?  Once the company approves, it will be credited
to your account.  I will come now.
Let's see the total earnings the company has made.
Before that let's see the sequence.  5 31 2026
December 31 2025 & March 31 2025. So
friends, this is it for our year end year comparison
and this is it for our quarter end
quarter.  Let us see what the company earned in this quarter.
See, the company has
earned Rs
661,870 and how much it earned in the last quarter was Rs
66150. You
can see that quarter after quarter there
is a slight jump in profit, friends, which we
will call revenue and last year it was Rs 585,517,
so this is also a jump, friends, year after year,
quarter after quarter, there is a jump in both revenue.
Now to earn this much, the company has
spent Rs 6,7291,
so when we do income minus expense, it
shows a loss of Rs 28,238.  I have already told you
friends that it is not that easy to read the results of any company.
In this we have to
look at NPPA, friends.
We call NPP, this is called
Net Profit Provision and sorry NPA N
means NPA P means profit friends and
P means provision so in all this you will
add exceptional item provision
friends so after doing all this add weight you will
subtract tax weight everything friends so
see this profit and loss that
extra ordinary item tax weight everything has been
subtracted friends so this is that
profit friends
this is that profit which you will
see everywhere because
what do you say 71820 in the last quarter it was
and last year it was 6820
you will see year and year there is a good jump
friends but quarter and quarter the
profit and loss before tax of the company
friends we call PAT has gone
down a lot so now let us come to
provision so see friends the provision is
of 17164.  Someday I will
bring a detailed video on how to read insurance and bank
results.  Now
friends let us come to EPS.  Friends, the EPS of the company is
10.97
for this quarter and for the previous quarter it was
13.25 and for the previous year it was 10.29, so you
can see that there is a jump in the year-end EPS as well
but quarter-end EPS is also
down and the same is the case with profit as well, friends,
year-end year there is a jump and quarter-end
quarter there is a downfall.  So if you
want a video on any company, please comment
friends.  If you liked the video,
please like and subscribe.  Thanks
friends.